Tip Top Copper Company records, 1900-1931
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Tip Top Copper Company records, 1900-1931
AZ 092
Tip Top Copper Company
Collection includes payrolls, reports, correspondence, financial records, legal papers, and miscellaneous materials pertaining to the Tip Top Mine in Helvetia Mining District, Pima County, Arizona.
1.25 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL:http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Organization
This collection is organized into two series:
I. General Records, 1903-1931
II. Ledgers, 1900-1926
Scope and Content Note
Collection includes payrolls, reports, correspondence, financial records, legal papers, and miscellaneous materials pertaining to the Tip Top Mine in Helvetia Mining District, Pima County, Arizona. There are also some personal letters to Joseph Chamrod, employee at the mine, and his family, dealing with stock grazing on the property.
Access Terms
Chamrod, Joseph
Mines and mineral resources -- Arizona -- Pima County
Mining corporations -- Arizona -- Pima County
Mineral industries -- Arizona -- Pima County
Copper mines and mining -- Arizona -- Pima County
Copper miners -- Arizona -- Pima County
Helvetia (Ariz.) -- History
Correspondence
Ledgers
Account Books
Container List
- Series I: General Records, 1903-1931
  - Legal papers, 1903-1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Financial records, 1903-1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence and miscellaneous papers, 1903-1931 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Series II: Ledgers, 1900-1926
  - Ledger, February-November, 1900 (Volume 1)
  - Ledger, 1900 (Volume 2)
  - Ledger, 1911-1912 (Volume 3)
  - Ledger, 1913 (Volume 4)
  - Monthly time book, 1907-1926 (Volume 5)